https://pursepatterns.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Atkinson Designs
Aunt Tam's Pattern Co.
Ric raC Bag Patterns
Robin Quilts, Etc.
UNIQUE Purse Patterns
V and Co.
Woopies Originals
On SALE ...
New Patterns ...
Featured Patterns ...
All Patterns ...
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Privacy Policy for PursePatterns.com.
What information do we collect?
When an order is placed, the following information is collected: Name, billing address, shipping address (if different), and email address.
Nnewsletter sign-up collects your email address and your name.
The newsletter database is separate from the order processing database, and the two functions (newsletter and checkout) are independent of each other.
The information you provide will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever.
During the checkout process, if you select the payment by credit card option, your credit card information will be securely transferred for processing using a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protected payment gateway directly with our merchant account provider.
For what do we use your information?
Mp>The ordering information we collect from you will be used for order processing (you will receive an order confirmation email, and another email when your order is shipped) and customer service (your email address will be used to contact you if there is any issue regarding your order.<.p>
You will receive an email from the USPS website with a tracking number for your order.
If you sign up for our email newsletter, your email address is only used for the express purpose of delivering the monthly newsletter. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future email newsletters, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
Your name, address, and email address are stored securely on our web server.
Your credit card information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our secure payment gateway provider’s database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights (and who are required to keep the information confidential).
Your credit card information is not stored in our web server database.
Do we use cookies?
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows for full functionality of our shopping cart. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and PursePatterns.com does not use cookies to collect personal information.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information.
Shopping Cart  [more]
Your cart is empty.
New Patterns  [more]
Featured  [more]
Mail Sack Pattern
*$12.00
Bow Tucks Tote Pattern$11.00
A Little Duffle Do It$8.00
Looking fordownloadablePurse Patterns?
AvailableatAmazon.com
Check outHenrietta'sHandbagsfor unique bags!
